<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Eric Kipnis</title>
    <description>My personal portfolio website</description>
    <link>http://localhost:4444/</link>
    <atom:link href="/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2017 22:29:26 -0400</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2017 22:29:26 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v3.4.0</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>Radicchio</title>
        <description>Radicchio is an open-source, server-side timer library developed in JavaScript for the NodeJS runtime. The library utilizes Redis to keep track of TTL and was published as a package on npm.</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 23 Dec 2016 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4444/side%20project/2016/12/23/radicchio/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4444/side%20project/2016/12/23/radicchio/</guid>
        
        
        <category>Side Project</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Travelers</title>
        <description>Travelers EDGE was a static website created for The Travelers Companies, Inc. for the 10th anniversary of the Travelers EDGE program. Developed with JavaScript and the HandlebarsJS templating language, my responsibilities included building a DevOps solution using Jenkins and AWS for automatic code deployment as well as assisting with the front-end development.</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 20 Dec 2016 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4444/work%20project/2016/12/20/travelers/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4444/work%20project/2016/12/20/travelers/</guid>
        
        
        <category>Work Project</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Bloxeo</title>
        <description>Bloxeo is an open-source, brainstorming and team-collaboration web application. It utilizes a JSON API back-end written using the ExpressJS MVC framework, a MongoDB NoSQL database and a ReactJS front-end. My main responsibilities for the project included server tasks ranging from unit testing to writing services and data modeling, as well as some work on the front-end.</description>
        <pubDate>Sun, 04 Dec 2016 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4444/school%20project/2016/12/04/bloxeo/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4444/school%20project/2016/12/04/bloxeo/</guid>
        
        
        <category>School Project</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Mealhero</title>
        <description>MealHero is an open-source, meal-planning application. It utilizes a JSON API back-end written in Elixir using the Phoenix framework, a PostgreSQL database and a ReactJS front-end. This is an ongoing passion project of mine and is constantly being worked on!</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 09 Feb 2016 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4444/side%20project/2016/02/09/mealhero/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4444/side%20project/2016/02/09/mealhero/</guid>
        
        
        <category>Side Project</category>
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
